Guide to The Women's Sports Foundation Records 1950-2019 (bulk, 1974-2018) MS 3199
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Women's Sports Foundation archives, 1974-2018; 25 Linear feet in 25 record cartons
  - Subseries I.A. Chronological files, 1974-2018; 22 Linear feet in 22 record cartons
    - NGWSD playbook [disassembled binder] (2 of 2). Digital files, 2003 (Digital folder MS3199, Digital folder Box16_F5)
      Contains digital files stored originally on floppy disk in Box 16 Folder 5. Files include Microsoft Word and Microsoft Excel files. Content of files include RSVP lists, staff contact information, correspondence, invitations, seating charts, and hotel reservation and room information related to the NGWSD 2003 event.
    - Title IX resource (2 folders), 2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6-7)
    - NGWSD, 2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 8)
    - Marketing, 1999-2007 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 9)
    - GoGirlGo! leadership summit, 2004 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 10)
    - Educational material: annual report, 2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 11)
    - Educational material: guides, 2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 12)
    - Educational material: posters [NGWSD], 2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 13)
    - Educational material: research studies, 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 14)
    - Major events: Sneaker Day, 2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 15)
    - NYAD, 2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 16)
    - WSE/ Sports Talk: regular editions, 2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 17)
    - Sportsgirl of the Year, 2004 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 18)
    - Superwomen, 2004 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 19)
    - Project to eliminate homophobia in sports, 2004 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 20)
    - Events, 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1)
    - [Playing Fair: A Women's Sports Foundation Guide to Title IX in High School and College Sports by Katheryn M. Reith], 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 2)
    - GoGirlGo! (3 folders), 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3-5)
    - WSE/ Sports Talk, 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 6)
    - Her Life Depends on It, 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 7)
    - PSA, 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 8)
    - Annual report, 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 9)
    - NGWSD, 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 10)
    - NYAD (2 folders), 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 11-12)
    - NYAD, 2005 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Battle of the Sexes, 2005 October 16 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 14)
    - WSE, 2005 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 15)
    - Annual report, 2004 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 16)
    - GoGirlGo! Atlanta, 2005 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 17)
    - Chicago GoGirlGo! open houses (1 of 2). 2 folders, 2005 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 18-19)
      Contains paper documents, programs, and CDs with open house information.
    - Chicago GoGirlGo! open houses (2 of 2). Digital files, 2004-2005 (Digital folder MS3199, Folder Box17_F19)
      Contains digital files originally stored on CDs in Box 17 Folder 19. CDs contained copies of identical files. Files include PDFs and Microsoft Word files. Content of files include flyers and GoGirlGo! promotional and informational material, posters, participant certificates, and activity and program guides for the GoGirlGo! events.
    - GoGirlGo! Chicago, 2005 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 1)
    - GoGirlGo! (3 folders), 2005 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 2-4)
    - GoGirlGo! news, 2005 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 5)
    - NGWSD, 2005 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 6)
    - It Takes a Team, 2005 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 7)
    - [Reports] (2 folders), 2005 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 8-9)
    - GoGirlGo!, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 10)
    - Billies, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 11)
    - GoGirlGo! Chicago (1 of 2), 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 12)
      Contains paper materials and two DVDs.
    - GoGirlGo! Chicago (2 of 2). Digital files, 2006 (Digital folder MS3199, Folder Box18_F12)
      Contains digital file originally stored on CD in Box 18 Folder 12. Digital file is an MPG video clip CBS Chicago 2 news clip on the GoGirlGo! program at a Chicago school.
    - GoGirlGo! San Antonio, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 13)
    - Events, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 14)
    - NGWSD, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 15)
    - General media, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 16)
    - NGWSD Count Me In - Congressional visits staff packet, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 17)
    - NGWSD Count Me In - Representative packet, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 18)
    - NGWSD Count Me In - Senator packet, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 19)
    - Team WSF, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 20)
    - Advocacy, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 21)
    - Awards and grants, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 22)
    - It Takes a Team (1 of 2), 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 23)
      Contains publicity material, posters, and two DVDs.
    - It Takes a Team (2 of 2). Digital files, 2006 (Digital folder MS3199, Reel Box18_F23)
      Contains digital files originally stored on DVD in Box 18 Folder 23. Format of files include PDFs and VOB video files. PDF files contain an education kit. Video clips contain educational and promotional materials from the It Takes a Team education campaign for LGBT issues in sport.
    - Newsletters, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 24)
    - WSF: A Force of Change, 2006 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 25)
    - NYAD, 2006 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    - Media, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - SuperWomen, 2006 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3)
    - GoGirlGo! news, 2006 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 4)
    - Annual report, 2006 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5)
    - Direct-mail sample packets (4 folders), 2004-2006 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 6-9)
    - Development: direct-mail sample packets, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 10)
    - Development: Annual report, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 11)
    - Development, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 12)
    - Development: membership (2 folders), 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 13-14)
    - Development: direct-mail sample packets, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 15)
    - Education: NGWSD, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 16)
    - Education: Title IX research report, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 17)
    - Education: Title IX, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 18)
    - Events: The Billies, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 19)
    - Events: NYAD, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 20)
    - GoGirlGo!: National, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 21)
    - GoGirlGo!: Atlanta, 2006-2008 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 22)
    - GoGirlGo!: Boston, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 23)
    - GoGirlGo!: Chicago, 2007 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 24)
    - Publications: newsletters (2 folders), 2007 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Advocacy/ public policy: advocacy, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3)
    - Advocacy/ public policy: athlete services, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 4)
    - Communications: branding, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - Development, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - Education: BJK IWSC [BJK International Women's Sports Center], 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 7)
    - Education: publications, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 8)
    - Research reports (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 9-10)
    - Invitations to NYAD, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 11)
    - NGWSD, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 12)
    - Events: Annual Salute (NYAD), 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 13)
    - Events: GoGirlGo! Atlanta challenge, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 14)
    - Events: Hall of Fame, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 15)
    - GoGirlGo! (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 16-17)
    - GoGirlGo!: Media, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 18)
    - GoGirlGo!: San Antonio, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 19)
    - GoGirlGo!: Billies, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 20)
    - Public relations: media coverage, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 21)
    - Public relations: Sports Museum, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 22)
    - Publications: newsletters, 2008 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 23)
    - NGWSD, 2009 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
    - Publications (2 folders), 2009 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 2-3)
    - Events, 2009 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
    - Equal Opportunity for Transgender Athletes: A National Think Take [disassembled binder], 2009 October 25-26 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 5)
    - Research Center search/ selection: Texas Tech RPC finalist, 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6)
    - Research Center search/ selection: Cal State University, Long Beach RPC finalist, 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 7)
    - Research Center search/ selection: Ithaca College RPC finalist, 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8)
    - Research Center search/ selection: University of Wisconsin RPC finalist, 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 9)
    - Research Center search/ selection: University of Michigan RPC finalist (2 folders), 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 10-11)
    - Research Center search/ selection: Penn State RPC finalist (2 folders), 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 12-13)
      Contains paper documents and two DVDs. The two DVDs are commercial files produced by Penn State Athletics and have not been digitally preserved by N-YHS.
    - RPC search: RPC planning, 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 14)
    - Events NYAD, 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 15)
    - NGWSD, 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 16)
    - Publications, 2010 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 17)
    - NYAD (2 folders), 2011 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 18-19)
    - Development - Summer Title IX appeal, 2012 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 20)
    - Education - SHARP: Title IX at 40 conference, 2012 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 21)
    - NGWSD, 2012 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 22)
    - NYAD, 2012 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 23)
    - Curriculum: ages 5-7 [GoGirlGo!], 2012 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 24)
    - Curriculum: ages 8-10 [GoGirlGo!] (2 folders), 2012 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Curriculum: ages 11-13 [GoGirlGo!], 2012 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 3)
    - Development, 2013 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 4)
    - Appeal (development), 2013 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 5)
    - Annual Salute, 2013 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 6)
    - BJK 70th birthday, 2013 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7)
    - Annual Salute, 2014 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 8)
    - Her Life III Executive Summary, 2015 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 9)
    - Her Life III full report (2 folders), 2015 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 10-11)
    - NYAD, 2015 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 12)
    - Athlete Leadership Connection (ALC), 2015 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 13)
    - Development, 2015 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 14)
    - Research, 2016 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 15)
    - Annual Salute, 2016 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 16)
    - Annual Salute, 2017 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 17)
    - The Pulse, 2017 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 18)
    - Development, 2017 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 19)
    - BXO infographic, 2017 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 20)
    - Participant infographic, 2017 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 21)
    - T. Vanderveer Fund, 2017 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 1)
    - Annual Salute, 2018 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 2)
    - Athlete Leadership Connection, 2018 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 3)
    - External institutions proposals/ requests: WSF corporate papers - library, 2004 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4)
    - External institutions proposals/ requests: Schlesinger Library (2 folders), 1992-2007 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 5-6)
    - A Proposal by the Amateur Athletic Foundation to Acquire the Women's Sports Foundation Papers [disassembled binder], 1994 June (Offsite-box 23, Folder 7)
    - [History project], 1981-2001 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 8)
    - WSF history pieces, 1994-2001 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 9)
    - Women's Day - Defense of Women, 1983 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 10)
    - New Agenda invoices, 1983 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 11)
    - Programs and events, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 12)
    - WSF legal correspondence, 1975-1984 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 13)
    - Reference request on Paula Carter Sperber, 2001 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 14)
  - Subseries I.B. Publications archive, 1981-2004; 3 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Subseries I.B includes files originally stored in the WSF office in vertical filing cabinets labeled "Publications Archives." The files contain various publications of the WSF, including official newsletters and sports magazines for young athletes. Materials date from 1981 to 2004.
    Files are arranged alphabetically by publication title and chronologically within each publication.
    - Annual reports (3 folders), 1988, 1992-2006 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 1-3)
    - Associate Newsletter (4 folders), 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 15-18)
      Contains issues of the Associate Newsletter, sent to the WSF's select group of Hall of Fame Associates, an affiliate of the international Women's Sports Hall of Fame created by the Foundation in 1980. The newsletter includes information on legislation regarding women's sports, conferences and workshops on sports, job opportunities, personal updates on Associates, and referrals to additional sources on women's sports. 1982 file also includes one issue of the WSF Corporate Report, sent to executives of corporations, advertising agencies, and public relations firms that are involved in women's sports and sponsorship.
    - Business and Women's Sports, 1979 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 19)
      Contains issues of the WSF's Business and Women's Sports newsletter, a quarterly corporate newsletter providing information on the interrelationships of women's sports and business.
    - The Champion, 1998-2001 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 4)
      Contains issues of "The Champion," WSF's newsletter for athletes.
    - Frontiers (3 folders), 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 20-22)
      Contains issues of "Frontiers," WSF's original quarterly newsletter. Contents of issues include fundraising information, names of advisory board and representative members, programming, and news on women's sports and on the organization.
    - GoGirl News (12 folders), 2004-2008 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 23-34)
      Contains issues of GoGirl News, the WSF's newsletter for young athletes.
    - GoGirl News, 2004-2008 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 5)
    - Headways, 1985-1989 Spring (Offsite-box 23, Folder 35)
      Contains issues of Headway, the WSF newsletter. Issues contain information on trustees and staff of WSF, travel and training funding, award recipients and application, programs, events, announcements, and women's sports news.
    - Headways, 1985 March (Offsite-box 91, Folder 41)
    - Headways (2 folders), 1989 Summer-1991 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - SportsTalk (10 folders), 1998-2004 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 3-12)
      Contains issues of SportsTalk, the WSF's newsletter for young athletes.
    - SportsTalk, 1997-2004 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 6)
    - Strides, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 42)
    - The Women's Sports Experience, 1988-2008 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 34)
    - The Women's Sports Experience (8 folders), 1992-1997 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 13-20)
      Contains issues of The Women's Sports Experience, a newsletter from the WSF. Issues contain information on WSF staff and trustees, fundraising, awards, scholarships, WSF publications, resources available on women's sports, and WSF events.
    - The Women's Sports Experience (6 folders), 1997-1999 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 1-6)
    - The Women's Sports Experience (33 folders), 2000-2007 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 1-33)
    - WSF Newsletter (3 folders), 1983, 1984 April, 1984 November (Offsite-box 91, Folder 43-45)
- Series II. Board of Trustees records, 1975-2010; 37 Linear feet in 37 record cartons
  Series II contains records of the governing bodies of the Women's Sports Foundation, including the Board of Trustees, the Executive Committee, the Advisory Board, and various Committees of the Board. Records include handbooks, correspondence, meeting agendas and minutes, reports, and biographical files. Material documents the governance and operations of the WSF from its founding through the 21st century, including Foundation objectives, programming, fundraising, location and staffing changes, leadership, and changes to the Board itself. Records date from 1975-2010.
  Arranged in four subseries:
  Subseries II.A. Board of Trustees minutes and handbooks
  Subseries II.B. Executive Committee records
  Subseries II.C. Advisory Board and Committee records
  Subseries II.D. Trustees biographical files
  - Subseries II.A. Board of Trustees minutes and handbooks, 1981-2009; 13 Linear feet in 13 record cartons
    Biographical / Historical
    The Board of Trustees is legally responsible for the operation of the WSF and establishes fiscal policy, assists in the acquisition of financial and human resources, and oversees the accomplishment of Foundation goals and objectives. Trustees consist of champion female athletes, prominent businesspersons, major benefactors, and leaders of women's sports organizations.
    Subseries II.A contains Board of Trustees meeting records, including meeting agendas and minutes, and Board of Trustees policy handbooks. Meeting records document WSF activities, priorities, staffing changes and decisions, and Trustee elections and voting over time. Duplication of certain meeting agendas and minutes records is present. Materials date from 1981-2009.
    Files are arranged chronologically.
    - Meetings, 1981 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 7)
      Contains file of Trustee meetings and minutes originally stored in the WSF office conference room vertical filing cabinets.
    - Updates and minutes, 1982 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 8)
    - Minutes [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1981 February 12-1993 June 20 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 9-10)
    - Meetings (2 folders), 1981-1990 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 11-12)
    - Minutes, 1982-1992 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 13)
    - Meetings, 1983 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 14)
      Contains files of Trustee meetings and minutes originally stored in the WSF office conference room vertical filing cabinets.
    - Minutes, 1984 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 15)
    - Documents, 1985 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 16)
      Contains correspondence, press releases, reports, and meeting minutes.
    - Meeting, 1986 February 8 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 17)
    - Meeting, 1986 September 21 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 18)
    - Address lists, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 19)
    - Meetings (2 folders), 1987 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 20-21)
      Contains minutes and reports from March, July, and September 1987 meetings.
    - Meeting, 1987 March 20 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 1987 July 13 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 1987 September 20 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 3)
    - Media plan (Bertini), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 4)
    - Meetings (4 folders), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 5-8)
    - Strategic planning, 1988 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 9)
    - Updates, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 10)
    - January meeting, 1988 January 9 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 1988 May 20 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 12)
    - Meeting (3 folders), 1988 October (Offsite-box 26, Folder 13-15)
    - Business plan for 1989 and long range goals for 1993, 1988 December 15 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 16)
    - Biographies and responsibilities, 1989 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 17)
    - Info, 1989 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 18)
    - Objectives evaluation, 1989 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 19)
    - Reports, 1989 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 20)
    - Snoopy poster, 1989 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 22)
    - Handbook sample [disassembled binder], 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco - handouts and business plan, 1989 January (Offsite-box 26, Folder 24)
    - Minutes, 1989 January (Offsite-box 26, Folder 25)
    - Meeting, 1989 January 5 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 26)
    - Meeting (1 of 2 folders), 1989 May (Offsite-box 26, Folder 27)
    - Meeting (2 of 2 folders), 1989 May (Offsite-box 27, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1989 May (Offsite-box 27, Folder 2)
    - Meeting agenda, 1989 May 24 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 3)
    - Trustee and Advisory Board update, 1989 August 4 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, 1989 September (Offsite-box 27, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 1989 October 2 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 6)
    - Trustee and Advisory Board update, 1989 October 18 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 7)
    - Calendar, 1990 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 8)
    - Golf company letter/ project, 1990 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 9)
    - Kilimanjaro confidence climb, 1990 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 10)
    - NGWSD publicity (news clips), 1990 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 11)
    - Non-profit survey trustee expenses and attendance policies, circa 1990 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 12)
    - WSF programs: a review, 1990 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 13)
    - Summary of programs, 1990 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 14)
    - Board of Trustees, 1990 January (Offsite-box 27, Folder 15)
    - Handbook [disassembled binder], 1990 May (Offsite-box 27, Folder 16)
    - Info packets, 1990 May (Offsite-box 27, Folder 17)
    - Meeting setups (3 folders), 1990 May (Offsite-box 27, Folder 18-20)
    - Meeting, 1990 May 20 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 21)
    - Trustee and Advisory Board updates, 1990 June 18 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 22)
    - Board of Trustees (4 folders), 1990 October (Offsite-box 27, Folder 23-26)
    - Info (4 folders), 1990 October 14 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 27-30)
    - Meeting, 1990 October 14 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 31)
    - Meeting agenda and materials, 1990 October 14 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 7)
    - Mailing, 1990 December 4 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 32)
    - NCAA President's letter mailed to Trustees, 1990 December 11 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 33)
    - Info, 1991 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
    - Lily of France (quotes for the hangtags), 1991 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 2)
    - Returned Trustee invoices, 1991 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
    - Sporting match, 1991 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 5)
    - Executive Director search, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 6)
    - Minutes (3 folders), 1991-1995 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 7-9)
    - Mailing for January 11 meeting, 1991 January 4 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 10)
    - Mailing, 1991 January 10 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 1991 January 11 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 12)
    - Votes from Indianapolis meeting, 1991 January 11 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 13)
    - Update, 1991 January 17 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 14)
    - Mailing, 1991 February 28 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 15)
    - Materials for NYC meeting with Sally Edwards, 1991 April 10 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 16)
    - Trustees, 1991 May (Offsite-box 28, Folder 17)
    - Memo re: lodging, 1991 May 18 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 18)
    - Mailing, 1991 May 20 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 19)
    - Meeting, 1991 May 20 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 20)
    - Ballots for stewards and handbook changes, 1991 June-August (Offsite-box 28, Folder 21)
    - Follow up mailing to Trustees, 1991 June 10 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 22)
    - Mailing, 1991 July 2 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 23)
    - WSF update mailed to Advisory Board and Trustees, 1991 July 9 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 24)
    - LSJ memo to Trustees, 1991 July 18 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 25)
    - BJK Contribution Award ballot and info sent to Advisory Board and Trustees, 1991 July-August (Offsite-box 28, Folder 26)
    - Ballot recap, 1991 August 14 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 27)
    - Advisory Board and Trustee mailing, 1991 September 10 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 28)
    - Ballot - Donna de Varona Honorary Trustee, 1991 September 30 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 29)
    - Trustees, 1991 October (Offsite-box 28, Folder 30)
    - Handouts from meeting, 1991 October 6 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 31)
    - Mailing - follow up to meeting, 1991 October 6 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 32)
    - Executive Headquarters and Hall of Fame Relocation Plan, 1991 October 6 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 17)
    - Mailing - Nominating Committee information, 1991 November 21 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 33)
    - Mailing, 1991 December 4 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 34)
    - PR plan, 1992 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 35)
    - Mailing, 1992 January 3 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 36)